hi folks so this is Matt again and we
大家好，再次是Matt，我们
are now going to talk about Vickrey
现在要谈论维克瑞
Clark groves mechanisms or VCG
克拉克格罗夫机制或VCG
mechanisms and these have become one of
机制，这些已成为其中的一种
the most well studied set of mechanisms
研究最深入的机制
in game theory and with good reason they
在博弈论中，并且有充分的理由，他们
have wonderful properties some very
有一些非常好的特性
interesting properties and let's talk a
有趣的属性，让我们来谈谈
little bit about the kinds of positive
关于积极的一点点
results will get now out of these
结果将从这些中得到
mechanisms before we go into the
在我们进入
detailed definitions and so forth so
详细定义等等
we're going to work in a quasi linear
我们将以准线性方式工作
setting and we're going to work here
设置，我们将在这里工作
remember now we have look at direct
记得现在我们看看直接
mechanisms where you society will have a
你的社会将有一个机制
choice rule and the payment rule based
选择规则和付款规则
on what preferences people report to the
人们向哪些方面报告
mechanism and the nice thing about VCG
机制和VCG的好处
mechanisms Vickery Clark groves
机制维克·克拉克树林
mechanisms is that they will have truth
机制是，他们将拥有真理
as a dominant strategy so people won't
作为主要策略，因此人们不会
have to worry about what other
还要担心其他
individuals are doing regardless of what
个人在做什么，不管
their preferences are the best thing
他们的喜好是最好的
they can do in terms of maximizing your
他们可以做到最大程度地
utility is to tell the truth and this
实用是说实话
mechanism is also going to choose
机制也要选择
efficient axis so choices here mean the
有效轴，因此这里的选择意味着
one we choose when we think about which
当我们考虑哪个时，我们选择一个
x and x maximizes the overall total sum
x和x使总和最大化
of utilities in a society it's going to
社会中的公用事业
pick those so it's not that it might not
选择那些，所以不是不是
be efficient in terms of making all the
在使所有
payments balanced but it's going to make
付款平衡，但这将使
efficient choices okay now these
高效的选择，现在这些
mechanisms in terms of the history of
机制的历史
this victory was the first to define
这场胜利是第一个定义
these in an auction setting so this is
这些是在拍卖设置中，所以这是
going to have a close relationship to
将会与
second price auctions and basically
第二价格拍卖，基本上
generalizes second price auctions to a
将第二次价格拍卖概括为
more general class of auctions known as
更一般的拍卖类别称为
victory auctions in the auction setting
拍卖场中的胜利拍卖
Clarke then generalized that to a more
克拉克然后将其推广到更多
general set class of settings and
一般设置类别的设置和
defined what was known as the pivotal
定义了所谓的关键
mechanism which is a special class of
机制是一类特殊的
these mechanisms and then groves gave
这些机制，然后格罗夫给了
basically the class of all such
基本上所有此类
mechanisms and and there's some nice
机制，还有一些不错的
properties of a more general class of
更一般类别的属性
these and so we'll look at these in
这些，所以我们将在
in more detail the nice thing is we're
更详细的是，我们
going to dominant strategies and
采取主导策略，
efficient choices and the quasi
有效的选择和准
linearity is going to be critical here
线性度在这里至关重要
and making sure everything works and so
并确保一切正常
we're looking at private values so
我们正在考虑私人价值，因此
conditional utility independence in
有条件效用独立性
general and we'll be looking at settings
一般，我们将研究设置
where we have a quasi linearity is going
我们有一个准线性的地方
to make things go for us okay in under
使事情顺利进行下去
you know some particular settings we'll
你知道一些特殊的设置
be able to get additional things like a
能够获得诸如
week budget balance condition interim
周预算余额状况临时
individual rationality other kinds of
个人理性其他
nice things coming out but more
好东西出来了，但更多
basically the the key ingredients here
基本上这里的关键成分
are going to be dominant strategies and
将成为主导策略，
efficiencies ok so let's start with a
效率不错，让我们从
general class of these mechanisms which
这些机制的一般类别
are known as growth mechanisms I'm after
被称为我追求的成长机制
Ted groves and so we're looking at
泰德·格罗夫，所以我们在看
direct mechanisms so this is going to be
直接机制，所以这将是
making a choice out of whatever our X
从X做出选择
set is and then the peas are going to be
设置是，然后豌豆将是
the P is going to be in RN again right
P将再次进入RN
so it's telling a payment for each of
所以它告诉每个人都付款
the individuals and the interesting
个人和有趣
thing about a growers mechanism is it
关于种植者机制的事情是
grows mechanism is going to be any
增长机制将是任何
mechanism of the following sort look at
以下排序机制
the announced utility functions each
每个公布的实用程序功能
person is telling us now what's their
人正在告诉我们他们是什么
evaluation function that's the their
评估功能就是他们的
private information so we get these
私人信息，所以我们得到这些
announcements so people are telling us V
公告，所以人们告诉我们V
hat 1 through V hat n which are telling
帽子1到V帽子n
us how do they value the different
我们如何看待与众不同
alternatives so society first of all is
替代品，所以社会首先是
going to make a choice which maximizes
将做出最大化选择
the total sum of those if that's unique
这些的总和（如果唯一）
then that ties this thing down exactly
然后把这个东西精确地绑在一起
sometimes there could be ties it's going
有时可能会有联系
to always pick something which is best
总是选择最好的东西
for society in terms of overall
对于社会而言
maximization then the key thing here is
最大化，那么这里的关键是
going to be the payment rule and what's
将成为付款规则，这是什么
the payment rule going to look like the
付款规则看起来像
payment rule for a given individual is
给定个人的付款规则是
going to be something which is going to
将会成为
depend on what the sum function of what
取决于什么的和函数
the other individuals announced so minus
其他人宣布减
I meaning
我的意思是
the vector of utility functions
效用函数的向量
announced by the other individuals other
由其他人宣布
than I and it's also going to have a
比我，它也将有一个
part here will subtract off the sum of
这里的部分将减去总和
the announced valuation functions
宣布的估值功能
evaluated at the chosen alternative by
在选定的替代条件下进行评估
society
社会
okay so society makes a choice we look
好吧，社会让我们做出选择
at how much does everyone else get you
其他人能给你多少
in terms of utility for that we can add
在实用性方面，我们可以添加
in some some other thing that doesn't
在某些其他事情上
depend on that given individual so
取决于那个给定的个人
sometimes it's going to be useful to add
有时添加会很有用
in other things and we'll talk about
在其他方面，我们将谈论
that in a moment anything which has this
一会儿，任何有这个的
structure to it is known as a grove's
它的结构被称为树丛
mechanism it's as a particular class of
机制是作为一类特殊的
mechanisms sometimes these are referred
有时提到这些机制
to as VCG mechanisms that name has more
作为VCG机制，该名称具有更多
recently been used to look at a
最近用来看一个
situation with a very specific payment
付款非常具体的情况
rule here and we'll talk about that in a
统治这里，我们将在
moment but this is a general class of
现在，但这是
Grove's mechanisms okay so now let's
格罗夫的机制还不错，现在让我们
look at Vickery Clark groves mechanisms
看看维格里·克拉克（Vickery Clark）的小树林机制
a special class which is also these go
一个特殊的班级，这些也是
by different names and different
用不同的名字和不同的
literature's on the economics literature
经济学文献
this was really known as a pivotal
这真的被称为关键
mechanism in part of the computer
部分计算机的机制
science literature and the game theories
科学文学与博弈论
literature more generally it's becoming
文学更普遍地
known as victory VCG mechanism
被称为胜利VCG机制
sometimes VCG is used to look at the
有时会使用VCG来查看
broader class but what's specialized
更广泛的阶层，但有什么专长
here is if you remember that each
如果您还记得每个
function we had so we had an H function
我们有一个H函数
H I of V hat - I that function now takes
V hat的HI-该功能现在需要
a very specific form in that specific
特定形式的非常特定的形式
form in particular is one where what we
形式尤其是其中一种
do is pick something which maximizes the
要做的就是挑选能最大化
sum of everyone else's utility so what
其他人的效用之和
would society choose if I were ignored
社会会选择我是否被忽略
and then look at the total sum of
然后看一下
utilities that would come out of that
从中得出的实用程序
and compare that to what people get when
并将其与人们何时得到的
I is taken into account right so this is
我被认为是正确的，所以这是
the choice that's made when I is being
当我被做的时候做出的选择
accounted for this is the choice that
占这是选择
would be made if we ignore die
如果我们忽略死亡将被制造
and this pivotal mechanism what it does
这个关键机制的作用
in terms of eyes payment is say how much
眼睛支付说多少
would everyone get if you ignored you
如果你忽略了你，每个人都会得到
how much does everyone else get if we
如果我们每个人都能得到多少
take you into account this is generally
考虑到你这通常
going to be a lower number right this is
将会是一个较低的数字，对，这是
going to have to be a lower number
一定要少一些
people can't be made better off by
人们无法通过改善而变得更好
including I in terms of the decision all
包括我在内的所有决定
that can do is distort things away from
可以做的是使事物远离
the overall Maximizer for these
这些的整体最大化器
individuals so this number is generally
个人，所以这个数字通常是
going to be a non negative number so
将是一个非负数，所以
this will be a payment that different
这将是不同的付款
individuals will be making into the
个人将融入
society okay
社会还可以
so let's have a look at what we end up
让我们来看看最终的结果
with here and so we've got this
在这里，所以我们有这个
structure on something which maximizes
在最大化的东西上的结构
overall utility and a particular payment
整体效用和特定的付款
scheme and so what you get paid is
计划，所以您得到的是
everyone's utility under the allocation
每个人的效用分配下
that's actually chosen except your own
实际上是您自己选择的
you get that as the direct utility and
您将其作为直接实用程序，并且
then you get charged everybody's utility
那么你就被指控每个人的公用事业
so when we take off this minus P I what
所以当我们减去这个负PI时
you're going to be charged is how much
你要收费的是多少
everyone else would have gotten in this
其他人都会陷入困境
world where they didn't have to take you
他们不必带你去的世界
into account less what they're getting
考虑少他们得到的
in the world where they do have to take
在他们必须采取的世界
you into account and so we can think of
您考虑在内，所以我们可以想到
this as the social cost of an individual
这是个人的社会成本
I right so this is social cost of I what
我是对的，所以这是我的社会成本
does that mean that means having I
那是否意味着有我
present imposes some change in utility
目前对实用程序造成了一些改变
for the other individuals individuals
对于其他个人
are paying their social cost okay who
付出他们的社会成本好吗
pay zero in this world well people who
在这个世界上付出零
end up not affecting the outcome at all
最终根本不影响结果
so the presence or non presence their
所以他们的存在或不存在
announcement of their utility function
公布其效用功能
didn't affect things overall um so who
总体上没有影响事情，所以谁
pays more than zero
支付多于零
pivotal agents who make things worse by
使事情变得更糟的关键人物
existing so there are situations where
存在，所以在某些情况下
the fact that they existed actually
他们实际上存在的事实
change the outcome in a way that made
以某种方式改变结果
the individuals were
个人是
Soph who winds up getting paid while
索菲（Soph）最终获得报酬
people can in some circumstances under
人们在某些情况下可以
some of these mechanisms gets paid by by
其中一些机制由以下机构支付
making things better off for other
使事情变得更好
individuals okay one nice thing about
个人还好，关于
these mechanisms and the the beauty of
这些机制和美丽的
these mechanisms is that truth-telling
这些机制就是说真话
is going to be a dominant strategy under
将成为下一个主导策略
any growth mechanism including the
任何增长机制，包括
pivotal mechanism are these BCG
这些BCG是关键机制
mechanisms so when we have this basic
机制，所以当我们有这个基本
form the theorem tells us that truth is
定理告诉我们真理是
a dominant strategy and let's go through
主导策略，让我们经历一下
that so we'll first go through this
那我们先来看看
theorem and then we'll talk about a
定理，然后我们将讨论
converse near-miss as basically if you
几乎像你这样交谈未遂
want truth to be a dominant strategy in
希望真理成为主流策略
these settings with quasi linear
这些设置与准线性
preferences and private values it's
偏好和私人价值观
going to have to be a growth mechanism
必须成为一种增长机制
so these mechanisms will be dominant
因此这些机制将占主导地位
strategy and basically in this setting
策略，基本上在这种情况下
they will be the only dominant strategy
他们将是唯一的主导策略
mechanisms that result in inefficient X
导致X效率低下的机制
choices okay
选择还可以
so let's have a look at this so let's
让我们来看看这个，让我们
look at to try and see why this theorem
看一下尝试看看为什么这个定理
is true let's think of what i's problem
是真的，让我想想我的问题
is so what they're getting is they're
所以他们得到的是
getting this is their true utility VI
得到这个才是他们真正的工具VI
and they're thinking about what they
他们在想他们
should announce right so I is choosing
应该宣布正确，所以我选择
what what function should I tell the
我应该告诉什么功能
mechanism that I have in terms of my
就我而言的机制
utility function so that's going to
实用程序功能，以便
affect the outcome and it's going to
影响结果，它将
affect the price and this is their
影响价格，这是他们的
overall utility so they want to choose
整体实用性，所以他们想选择
the announcement to maximize the utility
最大限度地发挥效用的公告
function so let's have a look at the
功能，让我们来看看
groves mechanism substitute in for this
格罗夫斯机制代替了这一点
and then see what people's incentives
然后看看人们的动机是什么
are in that world
在那个世界上
so under groves mechanism your payment
所以在格罗夫机制下您的付款
rule looks like this so it looks like an
规则看起来像这样，所以看起来像
H I minus the V hat and when we take the
HI减去V帽，当我们拿
minus of the overall thing we end up
减去整体的结果
with this so uh there should be an I
有了这个，所以应该有一个我
here subscript I so when we look at that
我在这里下标，所以当我们看那个
payment scheme the individual is
个人的付款方式
choosing this to maximize their overall
选择这个来最大化他们的整体
utility um so first of all notice that
实用程序，所以首先请注意
this thing does not depend on V hat I
这个东西不取决于我的帽子
so maximizing net is equivalent to
所以最大化净额等于
maximizing this when we ignore it okay
当我们忽略它时可以最大化它
so now we've boiled this problem down to
所以现在我们把这个问题归结为
solving this problem
解决这个问题
okay so maximize VI of the chosen
好吧，所以最大化所选VI
alternative is a function of what you
替代的是你所要的功能
announce plus the other peopls announced
宣布加上宣布的其他人
utilities okay now one thing to notice
实用程序现在可以注意一件事
is this begins to look like you're just
这开始看起来像你只是
trying to maximize the overall sum of
试图使...的总和最大化
utilities where yours is the truthful
实用的实用工具
and then everyone else's is what the
然后其他人的是
announced one is so I would like to
宣布一个，所以我想
choose a glute declaration which would
选择一份简短的声明
lead to lead the mechanism to pick an
导致牵头机制
outcome which is going to maximize this
结果将最大化
overall thing right so what you'd like
总体来说是正确的，所以您想要什么
to do is choose a V hat I that will lead
要做的是选择我会领导的V型帽
the mechanism to make a choice which
做出选择的机制
solves this problem okay so if we go
解决这个问题好吧，如果我们去
back and look at this problem
回来看看这个问题
maximizing overall the V hat I is
使我的V帽总体上最大化
equivalent to saying let's try and get
相当于说让我们尝试获得
the mechanism to choose an X which will
选择X的机制
maximize this overall if the if that
如果可以的话，将整体最大化
declaration gets an X that which
声明得到一个X
maximizes this then that's certainly
最大化这个，那肯定是
doing it as well as possible
尽可能做到最好
now remember under a Grove's mechanism
现在记得在格罗夫的机制下
the X of the V hat I is something which
V形帽子的X我是
mark maximizes exactly the sum where
标记精确地使总和最大化
what you've done is put in your
您所做的已放入您的
announced utility if you want to get
宣布实用程序，如果您想获得
them to to do it with respect to your
他们这样做是为了尊重您
true utility then the way in which to do
真正的实用工具，然后做的方式
this is to have your announced utility
这是您宣布的实用程序
be equal to your your true utility and
等于您的真正效用，并且
then they'll be maximizing exactly the
那么他们将完全最大化
function that you want them to be
您希望他们成为的功能
maximizing and that means that truth is
最大化，这意味着真理是
a dominant strategy right so the girls
占主导地位的策略，所以女孩
mechanism will choose X in a way that
机制将以以下方式选择X
solves this maximization problem
解决了这个最大化问题
precisely when V hat is equal to VI
正好在V hat等于VI
therefore truth is a dominant strategy
因此，真理是主导策略
so this is a a this deceivingly simple
所以这是一个看似简单的
proof so it takes a while to go back
证明，所以需要一段时间才能返回
through this convince yourself it's true
通过说服自己，这是真的
but the basic idea here is the payment
但这里的基本思想是付款
that a given individuals have has is
给定的个人拥有的是
essentially what everyone else's
本质上是其他人的
announced utility function is and
宣布的效用函数为
whether those are truth
这些是否真实
or not from their perspective what
从他们的角度来看
they're getting in terms of an outcome
他们正在取得结果
is something which then maximizes the
然后可以最大化
overall total sum of utilities because
公用事业的总和，因为
what they're doing is maximizing their
他们正在做的是最大化他们的
true utility plus what other people have
真正的效用加上其他人拥有的
told the mechanism their utility
告诉该机制其效用
functions look like and by being
功能看起来像是
truthful they get an outcome which
说实话，他们得到的结果
maximizes that overall total sum which
使总的总和最大化
indeed is the best they can do in terms
就他们而言，确实是最好的
of maximizing their utility given this
鉴于此，最大化其效用
payment rule so the nice thing about
付款规则，关于
these VCG mechanisms or in general two
这些VCG机制，或者通常是两种
groves mechanisms is they align the
格罗夫机制是他们对齐
individuals and sent 'iv with the
个人，并与
society's incentives by making sure that
通过确保
the payment rule accounts for what their
付款规则说明了他们的
decision choice is what the impact of
决策选择有什么影响
their announcement is on everyone else's
他们的公告在其他人的
utility okay um now the uniqueness of
实用程序好吧，现在的唯一性
these things in terms of being the
这些东西是作为
converse theorem there's a theorem by
逆定理有一个定理是
Greene in the fall from the late 1970s
从1970年代后期开始秋天的格林
or the 80s which then says that there's
或80年代然后说
a converse here so suppose that that for
在这里相反，所以假设
any utility function it's so each
任何效用函数都是这样
individual could have any possible
个人可能有任何可能
utility function over the public
公众的效用函数
decision or the non-monetary decision so
决定还是非货币决定
domain is going to be rich in a very
领域将非常丰富
particular sense that people could have
人们可能有的特殊感觉
any possible utility ordering a utility
订购实用程序的任何可能的实用程序
function over the set of alternatives
在选择集上起作用
then we'll say that a mechanism that's
那么我们会说一种机制
efficient so it's choosing a decision as
高效，所以它选择一个决策
a function of the announced preferences
公布的偏好的功能
which maximizes the overall utility
最大化整体效用
that's going to have truthful reporting
这将有如实的报告
as a dominant strategy for all agents
作为所有代理商的主要策略
and preferences only if it's a growth
和偏好，只有在增长的情况下
mechanism so the payment rule has to
机制，因此付款规则必须
look like what we said in terms of a
看起来就像我们所说的
growth mechanism that's the only way
唯一的增长机制
that you can be truthful for all
你可以为所有人诚实
possible announcements
可能的公告
of preferences so not only are the
偏好，所以不仅
groves mechanisms dominant-strategy
格罗夫斯机制主导策略
incentive compatible but if we require
激励兼容，但如果我们需要
efficient outcomes these are the only
有效的结果，这是唯一的
ones that work okay so I won't prove
可以的，所以我不会证明
this explicitly the proof is actually
这显然是证明
fairly straightforward you can find a
很简单，你可以找到一个
version in a survey I wrote on mechanism
我写的关于机制的调查中的版本
design on my website but in terms of
在我的网站上设计，但在
summary here so far what have we got
到目前为止，这里总结
groves mechanisms and a special class of
格罗夫机制和一类特殊的
those the pivotal mechanisms or VCG
那些关键的机制或VCG
mechanisms have really nice properties
机制具有非常好的特性
in terms of incentives truth is always a
就激励而言，真理永远是
dominant strategy
主导策略
the agents payments rules basically
代理商付款原则
align their incentives with the society
使他们的激励措施与社会保持一致
in terms of making sure that they're
确保他们是
taking into account their impact on
考虑到它们对
other individuals preferences and
其他个人的喜好和
utilities and therefore we end up with
实用程序，因此我们最终得到
efficient outcome choices so that
有效的结果选择，以便
internalized leads people to internalize
内部化导致人们内部化
the externalities and leads to an
外部性并导致
efficient choices over the XS now one
现在比XS更有效的选择之一
thing that is also important to
对...也很重要的事情
emphasize is that it might be that these
强调的是，可能是这些
mechanisms are not overall efficient in
机制在
the sense that we might have to charge
我们可能必须充电的感觉
the agents money in order to get this to
代理商的钱是为了得到这个
work so it could be that the sum of the
工作，所以可能是
payments the pis
支付pis
is greater than zero so that means that
大于零，这意味着
people are making a bunch of payments
人们正在付款
into the society and we're not giving
进入社会，我们没有付出
them all back to the society so either
他们都回到了社会，所以要么
we have to funnel them off to somebody
我们必须将它们集中到某人
who's not involved in any of the
谁不参与任何
decision product process or we're going
决定产品流程或我们要去
to have to burn that if we try and give
如果我们尝试付出就必须燃烧掉
it back that could change the incentives
回来可能会改变激励措施
that we've just aligned so nicely so the
我们调整得很好，所以
part of the issue about this is we've we
关于这个问题的一部分是我们
put these payment rules in which an
将这些付款规则放在其中
align incentives very nicely but in
很好地调整激励措施，但是
order to do that we might have to be
为了做到这一点，我们可能必须
charging agents a lot in terms of what
收费代理很多
their impact on this society is and in
他们对这个社会的影响是
order to get things to balance we might
为了使事情平衡，我们可能
have to give up some some nice
必须放弃一些好
conditions that we'd want so nice thing
我们想要的好东西的条件
about these mechanisms dominant
这些机制占主导地位
strategies and that's why they've been
策略，这就是为什么他们一直
studied so extensively
研究如此广泛
there's a number of settings where they
他们有很多设置
form nice benchmarks and have really a
形成不错的基准，并且确实具有
long list of nice properties there are
不错的属性的清单很长
other settings where they serve as a
其他设置作为
benchmark and don't satisfy all the
基准，并不能满足所有
conditions we'd want and that generally
我们想要的条件，通常
has to do with the the balanced kinds of
与平衡的种类有关
conditions of the payments and the the
付款条件和
idea that sometimes people will be
有时人们会
charged even if they would rather not
即使他们宁愿不收费
participate in the mechanism so we might
参与该机制，因此我们可能
want to think about it the
想想一下
directionality conditions balance
方向性条件平衡
conditions and other kinds of things so
条件和其他种类的东西
we'll take a look at these in more
我们将在更多内容中进行介绍
detail and context and that'll be our
细节和背景，这将是我们的
next thing up
下一件事